- 几点了?abc- 4:30
- What time?abc- 4:30.
怎么这么晚?
Why so late?
社会学补考
Make-up test in social studies.
你星期六请shelby来吗?
Did you invite shelby for saturday?
不请
No.
要我打给她吗?
Do you want me to call Her ?
打电话请12岁的小姑娘来过夜abc这主意真不错
yeah, that'd be great. You callingabca 12-year-old girl for a sleepover.
没什么
It'll be fine.
这样吧 你打给你的朋友abc我就打给我的朋友
Make you a deal. I'll call aabcfriend when you call a friend.
这是你的生日 想做什么就去做吧
It's your birthday. Do what you want.
谢谢 再见
Thank you. Bye.
再见
Bye.
- 你忘东西了?abc- 没有
- What did you forget?abc- Nothing.
那你回来干嘛?
Then why'd you come back?
因为我住在这儿
'Cause I live here.
得了Samantha 你要迟到了
Come on, samantha, you'reabcgonna be late for school.
你说什么呢? 现在是4:30
What are you talking about? It's 4:30.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
我...
I, uh...
只是累了
Tired, I guess.
怎么了?
what's wrong?
我不知道
I don't know.
好极了 我都知道了
Great. That's all I need to know.
你迟到了! 好 拜拜
You're late! Okay, bye.
37岁男性 复发的一过性黑矇
37-year-old male withabcrecurring blackouts.
告诉他把龙舌兰换成波本威士忌
Tell him to switchabcfrom tequila to bourbon.
对我挺管用
Worked for me.
他看过的三个医生已经排除了酒精和毒品
The three doctors he's already seenabcalready ruled out drugs and alcohol.
那就是癫痫 告诉他买个曲棍球帽...
Well, then it's epilepsy.Tellabchim to buy a hockey helmet--
脑电图无异常 CT也没事
eeg's clean. So is the ct.
放松点
Relax.
得到了收养机构的批准abc不代表你得到了生母的认可
Just because you got approved by an adoption agencyabcdoesn't mean you'll get approved by the birth mother.
你是单身母亲
You're a single mom.
虐童被判无罪的夫妇都比你优先
That puts you somewhere belowabccouples acquitted in day care scandals.
不客气 House
You're welcome, Dr. House.
这个病历很有意思
It is an interesting case.
你几点去见那个妈妈?
What time are you seeing the mom?
你的人是不是还在跟踪我?
Are you having your guy follow me?
我对你当妈妈的社会价值大加鄙夷abc而你的回应只是一点讽刺
I just trashed your social value as aabcmother, and all I got was a little sarcasm.
这说明你觉得不需要自我辩护
It means you don't feelabcthe need to defend yourself,
也就是说你不为收养孩子担心
which means you're notabcworried about getting a kid,
也就是说你已经有一个孩子了
which means you've already got one.
我们11点见面
We're meeting at 11:00.
她还有两周就要生个女儿
She's due to deliver aabcbaby girl in two weeks.
那个妈妈肯定乐于abc把病恹恹的孩子交给一个医生
I'm sure the mom'll be thrilled toabchand her crack baby off to a doctor.
孩子没病
She's not a crack baby.
不是 那妈妈非常健康
No, mother's perfectly healthy.
她为了继续破译人体基因组abc不得不放弃她的孩子
She just had to give up the baby in orderabcto continue her work on the human genome.
她承认她曾经用过毒品
She confessed to some past meth use.
她不承认的才更有意思
What they don't confess to isabcalmost always more interesting.
这是不对的
This is a mistake.
因为不了解的小孩会有你不知道的问题
Because a kid you don't know may haveabcsome problems you don't know about
会遗传给孩子?
that she may have passed on to a kid?
因为你是个控制欲强的自恋狂
Because you're a controlabcseeking narcissist.
在工作上这倒不算坏事
Which is fine, good even, in some jobs.
但是你没有足够的准备去照顾孩子abc更别说是次品小孩了
But you're not equipped to handle aabcreal kid, never mind a factory second.
你在哪里见她?
Where are you meeting her?
在一个"跟踪我 报销时abc杜撰的泌尿科医生又买了条游船"的地方
In a little place called "follow me and yourabcurologist will be buying himself a new yacht."
他们跟你解释退货条款了吧?
They explained theabcreturns policy, right?
比买电子游戏的条款还恶劣
It's worse than video games.
我不会改变主意的
I'm not changing my mind.
可能是脑震荡的后遗症
could be post concussion syndrome.
连脑震荡都没有过
Not without a pre-concussion.
选个数
Pick a number.
干嘛?
For what?
Cuddy赌局 她得到批准了
Cuddy pool. She got the nod.
孩子14天就要生了
Little tweaker's due in 14 days.
大好的消息啊...我觉得
That's great news... I think.
是好消息
It's good news.
大好的消息是她坚称她不会改变注意
The great news is she insisted thatabcshe's not gonna change her mind,
也就是说她确实想过要改变主意
which means she's actuallyabcthought about changing her mind,
也就是说她不确定能不能做个好母亲
which means she's not sureabcshe's ready to be a mom,
也就是说她没有准备好成为一个母亲
which means she's not ready to be a mom,
也就是说她快要改变主意了
which means she's gonna change her mind.
唯一的问题就是什么时候
The only question is when.
100块买进
$100 buy in.
小于七天就是接下来的七天
Less than seven meansabcthe next seven days.
但是她想孩子都想了三年了
But she's been dying forabca kid for three years.
现在怎么可能放弃
No way she's gonna back out now.
没有这个选项
Not one of the options.
轻微中风可以导致一过性黑矇和记忆丧失
Mini strokes can causeabcblackouts and memory loss.
九小时远远超过了轻微中风的发病时间
Nine hours is a lot of timeabcto be out for a mini stroke.
在CT上能发现留下的残留损伤
And there'd be residualabcdamage on the ct.
男人在家做消费者产品测试
guy works at home as aabcconsumer product tester.
可能会暴露在毒素下导致短期记忆丧失
He could've been exposed to a toxinabcthat caused short term memory loss.
而不会显示在图像上
Wouldn't show up on imaging.
海绵窦血栓形成可导致abc失神发作和记忆丧失
Cavernous sinus thrombosis couldabcabsence seizures and memory loss.
我选七到十四
I'll take 7 to 14.
有一个人玩了
We have a player.
你刚说过这是好消息 你又要赌她放弃?
You just said it was great news.abcNow you want to bet against her?
只有她不放弃才是好消息
It's only great news if sheabcwants it to be great news.
House比我们任何一个都了解她
House knows her better than any of us.
我想匿名
I'd rather usea pseudonym.
有想法!
Good thinking.
我说她见了那个妈妈就会开溜了
I say she's gonna meet the mom and bolt.
我赌她早早出局
I'm going for the early fold.
检查他的家里有没有毒素abc他的窦腔里有没有血栓
Check his home for toxins andabchis sinuses for thrombosises.
也许是摄入了过量咖啡因
Maybe he oded on caffeine.
可他没有喝咖啡 只是闻而已
Apparently he didn't drink theabccoffee. He just smelled it.
他们刚搬来吗?
Did they just move here?
六年前
six years ago.
没这么抚养孩子的
This is no way to raise a kid.
他是个单身父亲
He's a single dad.
他一定在尽最大努力
I'm sure he's doing his best.
也就是为什么单身人士不该养孩子
Which is why singleabcpeople shouldn't have kids.
你对Cuddy收养孩子有意见?
You got a problem withabcwhat cuddy's doing?
你觉得单身母亲不能...
You think singleabcmothers can't--
我觉得传统家庭就是骗人的
I think theabctraditional family is a fraud.
甚至已婚妈妈也算是单身妈妈
Even married moms are single moms.
爸爸只是付帐单 顶多在睡前讲故事abc不至于让自己内疚致死
Daddy just pays some bills and reads justabcenough bedtime stories to not kill himself out of guilt.
我爸爸就不错 自从我妈妈死后...
My dad was great.Afterabcmy mom died--
他可能是个例外
he might be the exception.
话说回来 你已经够糟糕的了
On the other hand, youabcare fairly screwed up.
没有酒精 没有药物 没有毒品
No booze, no meds,no drugs.
也没有风景 楼空了一半
And no view. Building's half-empty.
他宁愿窗外是收费站也不选公园
He'd rather have a view ofabcthe turn pike than the park.
窗外是公园可能要贵一半
Park views are probably 50% more.
看了这个地方后abc你还不信他是个实用主义者?
You're the surprised the guy's aabcpragmatist after looking at this place?
他不是实用主义者 他是苦修者
Guy's not a pragmatist.abcHe's a flagellant.
看上去像霉菌
Looks like mold.
要是妈妈打扫的 就干净多了
Mom would've cleaned better.
暴露在某些霉菌中可导致短期记忆丧失
exposure to certain types of moldabccan cause short term memory loss.
你们俩都要做测试
We're testing both of you.
我感觉挺好的
I feel fine.
也许 但我们要谨慎
I'm sure you are. We'reabcjust being cautious.
除了学校和家 你们还去哪儿?
So where do you guysabcgo other than home and school?
哪儿也不去 爸爸在家工作 我去学校上学
Nowhere. Dad works atabchome,and I go to school.
有没有运动 朋友 旅行?
What about sports,friends, travel?
就像我说的 爸爸在家工作 我去学校上学
Like I said, dad works atabchome,and I go to school.
妈妈不在身边一定很难吧?
Must be hard notabchaving your mom around, huh?
事故发生时 我只有四岁
I was only four whenabcthe accident happened.
我知道你们肯定常常想念她的
Still, I'm sure youabcboth miss her sometimes.
也不是
Not really.
你太坚强了
You're strong.
我只是觉得死没什么大不了的
No, I just don't get what the bigabcdeal about death is, you know?
哦
Yeah.
她怎么样?
How is she?
身体很健康
Physically, she's fine.
但神经兮兮的
Mentally, she's weird.
她被她爸爸吓坏了
I'm sure she's just freakedabcout about her dad.
Harmon先生?
Mr. Harmon?
Harmon先生
Mr. Harmon.
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
我约了人 我必须去
I have an appointment. I have to go.
你在治疗中 几项检查结果还没出来
We haven't finished with your treatment.abcWe're still waiting on some test results.
我约了人
I have an appointment.
不好意思 你要改时间了
Sorry, you're gonna have to reschedule.
我必须要走
I really have to go.
Harmon先生 你知道你在哪儿吗?
Mr. Harmon, do you know where you are?
干嘛老阻止我?
Why are you trying to stop me?
看他的眼睛
His eyes.
是不是癫痫发作?
is he having a seizure?
瞳孔对光反射正常
His pupils are responsive.
我觉得他是在...睡觉
I think he's... asleep.
他只是在睡觉
he was just asleep.
说明没有记忆缺失
Means no memory loss.
梦游也不会要命
And sleepwalking doesn't kill.
除非他从窗户走出去了
Unless he walks out a window.
梦游不是诊断 只是个症状而已
Sleepwalking's not aabcdiagnosis. It's a symptom.
我们还没找出原因来...
As long as we can'tabcfigure out why--
压力诱导 失眠症 很多人都梦游
stress-induced insomnia.abcLots of people sleepwalk.
但不是在大白天 甚至脑袋都没沾枕头时
Not in the middle of the day beforeabcthey've even put their head on a pillow.
有可能是发作性睡病 病因有...
Could be some sort ofabcnarcolepsy.Which is caused by--
这通常有遗传病史
there's usually genetic history.
或是?
Or?
要是你知道答案的话 告诉我们不就行了
If you know the answer,canabcyou tell us the answer?
我不知道答案
I don't know the answer.
也就是又把我们绕回到...或是?
Which bringsabcus back to--or?
由环境因素触发
Some sort of environmental trigger.
也就是说?
Which means?
是毒素
It's a toxin.
所以我们要?
So we are?
被带到了一条烦人的路
Being lead down an annoying path.
我真的不知道要去向哪
I honestly don't knowabcwhere this is going.
只是跟着提示走
Just following the clues.
我们又回到原点了
We're right back where we started.
我们找到的霉菌不会导致这些症状
The mold we found doesn'tabccause these symptoms.
而且他的家中也没有什么其他因素了
And there's nothing else at his home.
还有?
And?
还有你很烦人
And you're obnoxious.
他从不出家门
He never goes anywhere else.
我们是怎么知道的呢?
Which we know because?
因为他这么说的
Because he says so.
因为他的女儿这么说的
Because his daughter says so.
因为他们没有理由撒谎
Because they have no reason to lie.
也就说明了他从不出家门...
Which proves heabcnever goes anywhere else...
当...
when...
他...
he's...
清醒的时候
conscious.
我的天哪 你说对了
Oh, my god,you're right.
他说他有约
He said he had an appointment.
下一次 让他去赴约
Next time, let him keep it.
送他回家 看看他梦游到哪里去了
Send him home. Seeabcwhere his dreams take him.
Becca?
是Cuddy医生?
Dr. Cuddy?
叫我Lisa 很高兴见到你
Lisa. Nice to meet you.
你要来一个吗?
Oh, you want one?
不了 谢谢
no thanks.
我停不了口
I can't stop eating them.
就像上瘾一样
I guess it's, like, a craving.
一天得吃一打
I must have, like,a dozen a day.
这是无咖啡因的
Oh, and this is decaf.
感觉如何?
How have you been feeling?
又累又胖还紧张
Oh, you know, tired,fat, nervous.
你有什么事情想问我的?
Is there, um, anything youabcwant to ask me?
事实上 只有一个问题
Uh, yeah, actually,Iabcjust have one question.
你想给她起个什么名字?
Um, what are you gonna call her?
还没拿定主意
Ah, I'm not sure.
事情挺突然的
It's all been rather sudden, you know?
挺喜欢Joy这个名字
I like joy.
不过还没定下来
But as I said,I haven'tabcreally decided yet.
那你有什么想问我的?
Well, is thereabcanything you want to ask me?
问吧
It's okay.
中介网站上有那么多候选父母
The agency web site isabcfilled with prospective parents.
他们的照片 自我介绍啦
Their photos,their biographies.
那么多好人
There's so manyabcwonderful people out there.
完美的夫妻
Wonderful couples.
为什么我要选一个单身妈妈?
Why did I choose a single mom?
我的祖母嫁了个待她猪狗不如abc的男人 过了37年
My grandmother was married for 37 yearsabcto a man that treated her like garbage.
要不是被我的衰爸甩了abc我妈也是这种下场
And my mom would've stayed married to myabcloser dad that long,but he dumped her.
我一直不明白她怎么会重蹈她妈妈的覆辙
You know, I never understood how you couldabcfall for the same crap as your mother.
直到我遇上了Tony
Then I met tony.
当我看到你的资料 医生 还是医院的头abc见到了你的照片...
When I read your bio, a doctor,a headabcof a hospital, I saw your picture...
我不希望她被失败者养大
I don't want her raised by a loser.
你得皮疹多久了?
How long have you had that rash?
不知道 几天?
I don't know. A few days?
关节痛不痛?
Have you had any joint pain?
痛啊 我怀孕了 浑身关节都痛啊
Yeah, I'm pregnant. All my joints hurt.
不应该全身关节都痛的
They shouldn't all hurt.
你磕过药吗?
Have you been using?
这7个月没有
Not in seven months.
自从知道自己怀孕了 就停了
Not since I found out I was pregnant.
需要检查一下
That needs to be checked out.
你确认不想要小孩?
You sure you don't want children?
别以为我们困在这 我又躺下了abc就意味着要深入了解对方
You know, just because we're stuck here andabcI'm lying down doesn't mean we need to get deep.
你担心会犯跟搞外遇一样的错误
You're afraid you'll make the sameabcmistake you made with your wife.
被抓到带着另一个小孩去球赛
Get caught taking someabcother kid to a ball game.
我喜欢现在的生活
I like my life as it is.
α波上升了
Alpha waves increasing.
行为有没有发生变化?
any change in demeanor?
没有 他只是站起来了
No, nothing. He just got up.
也许是血压变化的结果吧
Maybe it's a result ofabcthe blood pressure change.
δ波突然出现
Delta waves out of nowhere.
他在沉睡状态
He's now asleep.
大脑本该停止运动功能
Brain's supposed toabcturn off motor function.
要是他的大脑功能正常 我们就不会在这了
If the brain was doing what it wasabcsupposed to be doing, we wouldn't be here.
他要出门了 跟上
He's leaving. Come on.
她怀了38周了 你认为是感染性紅斑?
she's 38 weeks. Youabcthink it's fifth disease?
那是什么?
What's that?
是一种病毒感染 可以感染胎儿
It's a viral infection.abcIt can infect the fetus.
常见于怀孕前20周内
Usually in the first 20abcweeks of pregnancy,
免疫系统有问题的妇女
and in women who haveabctrouble with their immune system.
滥用药物史会危及免疫系统
History of drug abuseabccould've compromised her immune system.
我说了我已经断了7个月了
I told you I haven'tabcused anything in seven months.
我觉得像痱子
It does look more like a heat rash to me.
也许该看看血检报告
Yes, well,maybe we want toabclook at the actual blood tests.
当然
Of course.
- 她给你打工?abc- 是的
- She work for you?abc- Yeah.
这里所有人都给你打工
Everybody here works for you.
要生的时候 在这生可以吗?
When this happens for real,abcare you okay to deliver here?
- 可以啊abc- 太好了
- Yeah, sure.abc- Good.
血检正常
Blood work's normal.
- 再查一次abc- 查了两次了
- Test it again.abc- Tested it twice.
我给你开些治皮疹的局部乳霜
I'll get you some topicalabccream for that rash.
我要收她住院
I'm admitting her.
她没事啊
There's nothing wrong with her.
皮疹还可能是很多别的疾病的征兆
There are dozens of otherabcthings this rash could indicate.
我要彻底检查一下胎儿情况
I want a full fetal work up.
你失控了
you're losing it.
有孩子就会这样
That's wha happens when you have kids.
无休止的哭闹导致非理性的恐惧
Ceaseless crying and naggingabcleads to irrational fears.
但还没真的哭闹就这样了abc让人叹为观止
It's impressive that you didn't waitabcfor the actual crying and nagging.
她有带状皮疹 关节痛和滥用药物史
She had a lace pattern rash,jointabcpain, and a history of drug abuse.
换了你也会这样做的
You would've done exactly the same thing.
这样我就是个好爸爸了
Uh-huh, and I'd be an excellent father.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
吐奶
Baby barf.
妇产科发放免费样品
Maternity ward wasabchanding out free samples.
干得好
Well played, sir.
我现在就只好换了
You leave me no choice but to change.
- 换衣服 不是换想法abc- 这正是我想证明的
- My clothes,not my mind.abc- That's exactly my point.
到时候就不是我也不止一杯abc会是一天八次
It's not gonna be me and a cup.abcIt's gonna be eight times a day.
要是不能忍受这点污渍abc就不能忍受一个小孩
If you can't handle wearing thatabcstain, you can't handle a baby.
你干嘛这么在意?
Why do you even care?
我又不会叫你来帮忙照顾
It's not like I'm everabcgonna ask you to babysit.
我是个人道主义者
I'm a humanitarian.
我们该制止他
We should stop him.
我们就是想--
the whole point was to--
让他碾过无辜路人?
let him plow into someabcinnocent bystander?
他的脚没问题 眼也明显能视物
His legs are working. Obviously,abchis eyes are working too.
反应可能会慢啊
His reaction time could be slower.
- 他停车了abc- 我看到了
- He's stopping.abc- Yeah, I see.
- 他要做"梦爱"abc- 也许
- He's having sleep sex.abc- Maybe.
- 停在她旁边abc- 我会的
- Pull up to her.abc- I know.
- 那男的找你要什么?abc- 滚开
- What'd that guy want?abc- Piss off.
跟着他 她不是妓女
Go after him. She's not a hooker.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know?
你要我详细分析 还是制止他
do you want me to describe theabcclues, or do you want to stop him
把刚买的毒品吸完?
before he finishes offabcthe drugs he just bought?
看来他是个瘾君子
Apparently,rip's a coke fiend.
看来睡美人对"白粉公主"有意思啊
So sleeping beauty hasabca jones for snow white.
吸毒可解释嗜眠
coke explains the narcolepsy.
嗜眠可解释梦游
Narcolepsy explains the sleepwalking.
但这解释不了时空的断层
But it doesn't explain theabcripin the space time continuum.
吸毒导致梦游 梦游去吸毒abc吸毒又导致梦游
Coke leads to sleepwalking, which leadsabcto coke, which leads to sleepwalking.
那一开始的梦游是什么导致的?
What caused the first sleepwalking?
是清醒时吸的毒
The coke he took while he was wide awake.
他说他没有
Says he didn't.
又不是第一个撒谎掩饰吸毒的人
Wouldn't be the firstabctime somebody lied about drug use.
他不需要撒谎啊
he has no reason to lie.
他知道自己病了
He knows he's sick.
他的工作不要求药检
His job doesn't drug test.
没跟谁交往
No relationship.
女儿也不会发现
His daughter wouldn't find out.
也许他只是忘记了
Maybe he just forgot.
忘记自己吸过毒?
Forgot he did cocaine?
你觉得忘记比说谎更可信?
You're going with forgot over lying?
解释了一切啊
Fits.
可卡因解释了嗜眠
Cocaine explains the narcolepsy.
嗜眠解释了梦游
Narcolepsy explains the sleepwalking.
含在毒品里面的其他东西解释了失忆
Whatever is in the cocaine other thanabcthe cocaine explains the memory loss.
毒贩子在里面掺各种垃圾
Dealers cut this stuff withabcall kinds of garbage.
棒极了 我们立即开始治疗abc各种垃圾引发的疾病
Great, we'll start him on immediateabctreatment for all kinds of garbage.
你可以在实验室缩小范围
You can narrow it down in the lab.
我们没有样品
Not without a sample.
那去找样品
So get a sample.
你要我们去向毒贩子买毒品?
You want us to scoreabccocaine from a drug dealer?
很刺激
It's exciting.
很重的罪
It's a felony.
很有必要的
It's necessary.
她在这
there she is.
羊水状态不错
Amniotic fluidlooks good.
胎动很好 心跳很健康
Good fetal movement.abcHeart's beating nicely.
怎么了?
What?
像是肺部发育不全
It looks like pulmonary hypoplasia.
什么意思?
What's that?
宝宝的肺发育得不完全
The baby's lungs are under developed.
无法独立呼吸
She won't be able to breath on her own.
- 她会死吗?abc- 不知道
- She might die?abc- I don't know.
要是她今天生出来 就麻烦了abc但我们会确保此事不会发生
If she was born today,she'd be in trouble,abcbut we're not gonna let that happen.
我们给你用镁延迟分娩abc类固醇帮助胎儿肺部发育
We'll put you on magnesium to preventabclabor and steroids to grow the lungs.
幸亏Cuddy医生带你过来了
It's a good thing Dr.Cuddy brought you in.
你怎么知道毒贩子长什么样的?
how do you know what aabcdrug dealer looks like?
我没在吸毒 如果这是你想问的
I'm not doing drugs,ifabcthat's what you're asking.
我看到她手里有钱
I just noticed that sheabchad cash in her hand.
明显是从他那得来的
Obviously came from him.
当时明显没时间完成其他服务了
Obviously didn't have enough timeabcto perform any other services.
我怎么没注意她拿着什么
I didn'tabcnotice her holding--
她来了
there she is.
我们不是警察
Uh, we're not cops.
警察不会这么说吧?
Cops aren't allowed to say that,right?
他们也可以这么说
Yeah, they can say it.
如果你是警察 就会知道
But if you were a cop,you'd know that.
你要什么?
What do you want?
我想买点可卡因 行不
I would like to buy some cocaine, please.
绝对不是警察
Oh, definitely not a cop.
- 谢谢abc- 等等
- Thank you.abc- Wait.
好货
It's good.
你满意就好 毒枭 能走了么?
Glad you like it, pablo. Now can we go?
不行 你
No. You gave us the wrong stuff.
你胡说什么 给你的是顶级货
What are you talkingabcabout? You got my best.
我知道 我不要勾引新顾客上瘾的顶级货
I know. I don't want the good "getabcyour new customer hooked" stuff.
我要维持老顾客回头的货色
I want the stepped on "keep the oldabccustomer coming back for more" stuff.
你疯了么 娘们?
Are you crazy, bitch?
不 我只是个知道要什么的娘们
No, I'm a just a bitchabcwho knows what she wants.
看来你真对领养宝宝的事着迷了
Looks like this kid thingabcis really working out for you.
可大肆购物 却没有妊娠纹
All of the shopping,noneabcof the stretch marks.
别挑现在这个时候
Not a good time.
是哦 宝宝情况不妙
Right, kid's getting worse.
披着幸福外衣的祸害
Blessing in disguise.
虽说完全可以预计
Although a completely predictable one.
你领回流浪狗 就别被虱子吓到
You take in strays, don'tabcbe surprised by the worms.
还是穿着弄脏的衣服
Still wearing the sweater.
我没说你不固执
I didn't say you weren't stubborn.
我说你不够母性
I said you weren't maternal.
谢谢 走吧
Thank you. Go away.
你脾气更躁了
You're getting crankier.
宝宝病了
Baby's sick.
别怪我兴致不高
Sorry I'm not finding the fun in that.
真的值得吗?
Is it really worth it?
就为了追求无条件的爱?
Just for the pursuit ofabcunconditional love?
只有你才觉得是桩坏事
Only you could see that as a bad thing.
是虚假的 没有无条件的爱abc只有无条件的需求
It's a fake thing. There's no unconditionalabclove. It's just unconditional need.
别让这孩子成为你生物钟的牺牲品
Don't make this child aabcvictim of your biological clock.
牺牲品?
Victim?
- 你觉得孩子还是跟着生母好abc- 是的!
- You think she's betterabcoff staying-- - yes!
至少她知道自己做不了合格的母亲
Because at least she knowsabcshe's not qualified for the job.
我来猜
Let me guess.
我告诉她不准在屋子里玩球abc她不听话
I'm gonna tell her not to play ball inabcthe house, but she's not gonna listen.
不 我其实是想模拟abc她在你睡着时 偷偷放男朋友进来
No, actually,I was going for she sneaksabcher boy friend in while you're sleeping,
他想在桌子上干
and he wants to do it on the desk.
一开始她不同意 但显然她不太自爱
And at first she says no, butabcshe has issues with self-esteem.
摔坏了你得赔
You know you're gonna pay for that.
我教你认清现实 用智慧偿付
I'm paying for it right now. With wisdom.
走开
Get out.
我们发现了乳糖abc可卡因里掺了奶粉
We found lactose. The cokeabcwas cut with milk powder.
增加营养
Makes it nutritious.
奶粉没毒
Not much of a toxin.
除非他对牛奶过敏
It is if he's allergic to milk.
不 他冰箱里有牛奶
He's not. He has milk in his fridge.
他喜欢喝什么咖啡?
How does he like his coffee?
我不知道 有关系么--
I don't know.abcWhat does that--
橱柜里放着什么麦片?
what type of cereal's in the cabinet?
可可味之类
Cocoa-something.
怎么 这有什么关系?
Why, what does it matter?
他喜欢喝纯咖啡 牛奶是孩子喝的
He likes his coffeeabcblack. Milk's for the kid.
你怎么知道?
How can you be sure?
因为他喝牛奶的话abc就知道自己乳糖不耐了
Because if he drank the milk, he'dabcknow that he's lactose intolerant.
问问他 然后按过敏反应治疗
Ask him, then treatabchim for allergic reaction.
要是病情好转 我们就能提早收工了
If he gets better, weabcall get to go home early.
服用类固醇会损害抗感染能力
Steroids make you moreabcprone to infection.
这两星期里 你必须住院接受观察
You'll have to stay here for theabcnew two weeks so we can monitor you.
宝宝的肺 是因为...安非他命吗?
The baby's lungs, isabcthat because of... the meth?
有可能
Could be.
你一定很恨我
You must hate me.
如果你所做的一切都是对的abc我就没机会得到这个宝宝了
If you'd done everything right in yourabclife, I wouldn't be getting a baby.
你害怕吗?
You're not scared?
我很害怕
I am scared.
你有个完满的人生
You got, like,this perfect life.
还没有
Not yet.
怎么了?
What's that?
心律加快
Heart rate's climbing.
她怎么了?
What's wrong with her?
不是宝宝 是你
It's not the baby. It's you.
拿两单位O型阴性血来 马上!
I need two units of o-negative, stat!
妈妈二级胎盘早剥 引起大出血
The mother had a stage two placentalabcabruption. She's losing blood.
那提前分娩呗
So deliver the baby.
胎儿肺部差十周 未发育完整
The lungs are ten weeks premature.
那么说 现在分娩 宝宝有危险
So deliver now,risk the baby.
推迟分娩妈妈有危险
Deliver later,risk the mom.
这还不是你的宝宝abc由不得你决定
It's not your babyabcyet. It's not your call.
我说什么她都会照做
She'll do whatever I tell her to do.
不自爱
Self-worth issues.
这种性格会遗传的
That's genetic, you know.
应该现在分娩
You should deliver now.
没错
Right.
你是说真的?
Are you serious?
你不是么?
You're not?
- 你才告诉我--abc- 错误的答案
- You just told me--abc- the wrong answer.
你可以给妈妈输血 但不能给胎儿造一对肺
You can give the mom more blood.abcYou can't give the fetus more lungs.
她的肺也许能行
The lungs might work.
这是医学上的正确决定
It's the right decision medically.
那你找我干嘛
And yet you're he.
我是为了征求意见 而不是让你耍
To get your opinion,notabcto get jerked around.
看吧 问题就出在这儿
See, this is what's screwed up here.
你不肯定这是个正确决定abc但你却想这么告诉她
You're not sure that this is the right call, butabcyou are sure that this is what you want to tell her.
这个念头把你吓坏了abc因为并非出自医学动机
And that scares you becauseabcyour motives aren't medical.
内心深处的你不想要这个婴儿abc这个你想说服她杀死它
Some part of you doesn't want this baby,abcand that partwants to tell her to kill it.
这是不可能的
This is an impossible situation.
我只是建议她选择最保险的决定
I'm advising her toabctake the safest route.
没错
Right.
但不能解释你为什么换了衣服
Doesn't explain why youabcchanged your sweater.
我需要你的建议
I need your advice.
不是癌症
It's not cancer.
你能用意念切除脾脏吗?
Can you removeabcspleens with your mind too?
你想说的是Cuddy 病历只是个托辞
You're here to talk aboutabccuddy. The file is a pretext.
为什么你不主动找我说Cuddy?
Why the hell haven't you comeabcto talk to me about cuddy?
我都干了这么多出格事了
I've been doing allabcsorts of insane stuff.
如果她连你都搞不定 就别提一个宝宝了
If she can't handle yourabcinsanity, she can't handle a baby.
我正是这么想的
That's exactly my point.
不 你才不是
No, it isn't.
你觉得受到了威胁abc因为她升上高中了
You're feeling threatened becauseabcshe's going onto high school
只有你在原地踏步念八年级
and leaving you behind toabcrepeat the eighth grade.
因为她靠和数学老师上床换文凭
She's sleeping with the mathabcteacher to get a diploma.
收养孩子等同作弊?
Adoption is cheating?
他们会给她个假孩子不成?
Are they giving her a fake kid?
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
她即将和一个孩子相处abc但她和成人都相处不来
She gets to have a relationship with aabckid, but she can't handle one with an adult.
所以她想杀死她
So she's gonna kill it.
经你一说 豁然开朗
Well, it does seem cleaner.
我看过病历了abc她的决定是正确的
I've seen the file. She'sabcmaking a judgment call.
任何决定都是有原因的
Decisions are never made in a vacuum.
你让她痛苦也是有原因的
Just like your decision toabcmake her miserable.
你这么做是因为你不能abc扯着她的小辫子去沾墨水了
You're doing this because we no longer haveabcinkwells and cuddy doesn't have pigtails.
我啃你苹果的动机呢?
Why do you think I did that?
感觉如何?
How you doing?
我不知道
Not sure.
照你说的 我一直看着时钟
Been keeping an eye onabcthe clock like you said.
我想我没有丢失任何时间
I don't think I lost any time.
监测仪也证实了这点
The machinery agrees with you.
表明你的病症是可卡因引起的
That means your problems wereabccaused by the coke.
不敢相信 我竟然会吸毒
Can't believe I did coke.
你睡着了
You were asleep.
我选择去吸毒
I chose to do coke.
在睡梦中 你是没有责任的
In your sleep. You weren't responsible.
潜意识的我想这么做
Something inside me wanted to do it.
潜意识的我不认为这是错的
Something inside ofabcme didn't think it was wrong.
这和做梦一样
It's like a dream.
我们在梦中做的事情abc都是清醒时不会做的
We all do stuff in our dreamsabcwe wouldn't do when we're awake.
我不是
I don't.
这是什么?
What's that?
我睡着了 弄伤自己?
Did I fall asleep and hurt myself?
我看不到伤口
I don't see any cuts.
因为根本没有
Because there aren't any.
我想...
I think...
你在流血汗
you're sweating blood.
病人的毛孔渗血
Guy's bleeding out of his pores.
这告诉我们什么?
What does that tell us?
除了不想带他打棒球abc以及他命不久矣以外?
Other than you don't want to playabcbasketball against him and he's dying?
可卡因和过敏不是病因所在
and neither cocaine orabcallergies are the answer.
是系统性疾病
it's gotta be systemic.
也许是出血病毒?
Hemorrhagic virus, maybe?
你指伊波拉出血热?
you think it's ebola?
他的白血球数应该高过天花板
His white blood cell countabcwould be through the roof.
不是感染
It's not an infection.
弥散性血管内凝血?
D.I.C.?
凝血指标正常
Coags are normal.
是癌症
It's cancer.
- 白血病可以解释一切abc- 没有发烧
- Leukemia explains everything.abc- no fever.
- 出血abc- 体重没有减轻
- The bleeding.abc- No weight loss.
- 皮疹abc- 没有头痛
- The rash.abc- No headache.
全身疲乏
The fatigue.
白血病能从血常规中看出来
Leukemia'd be obvious from the cbc.
白血病经常会呈假阴性
Leukemia has falseabcnegatives all the time.
我们有4个理由支持abc4个理由反对白血病
So we have four reasons forabcleukemia, four reasons against.
1个反对理由就够了
Only need one against.
没错 如果有一个理由abc指向其它病的话
Yeah, if we had oneabcreason for anything else.
去做骨髓活检
Go do a bone marrow biopsy.
你会怎么做?
What would you do?
我认为...
I think...
我认为你应该等下去
I think you should wait.
但是等下去...我可能会死
But if I wait... I could die.
你可能会有危险 但--
There would be moreabcdanger for you, but--
这是你作为一位医生abc还是一位母亲的决定?
is this your opinion asabca doctor or as a mother?
这是我的医学建议
It's my medical opinion.
- 这是我的个人建议--abc- 我不想等
- It's my personal opinion--abc- I don't want to wait.
只要一星期就够了
It might only be one week.
我们会一直给你输血
We will keep you on plasma.
这不是我的宝宝
This is not my baby.
为了这个愚蠢的错误abc我已经失去了九个月
I have already sacrificed nineabcmonths for this stupid mistake.
我不想失去更多
I don't--I don't want toabcsacrifice any more.
Becca 你征求我的意见abc因为你想作出正确抉择
Becca, you asked my opinion becauseabcyou wanted to do the right thing.
你放弃宝宝的抚养权abc因为不想重复母亲和外婆的错误
You are giving up this baby because you don't wantabcto make the mistakes your mom made, her mom made.
现在你有机会打破这个循环abc为宝宝奉献
You have a chance to break this cycle,abcto do something great for this baby.
不
No.
躺着别动
I need you to hold still.
慢着
Wait.
你试用过晒黑霜或美黑喷雾吗?
Have you been testing anyabctanning creams or sprays?
没有
No.
这不是晒黑
It's not a tan.
说明不是白血病
Means it's not leukemia.
检测证实是肾脏衰竭 末期
chem panel confirms kidneyabcfailure, end stage.
给他做透析了吗?
Got him on dialysis?
血压太低
Bp's too low.
糟糕
Too bad.
顶多只剩下一两小时解决这个问题了
It would've been nice to have moreabcthan an hour or two to solve this thing.
血色素沉着症?
Hemachromatosis?
- 他的睾丸很小么?abc- 不 硬皮病
- He have tiny testes?abc- No. Scleroderma.
他的皮肤变黑了 而不是变白
His skin's darker,not lighter.
虽然这么一问一答很带劲abc但病人全身毛孔正在出血
As much fun as 20 questions tends to be,abche's blowing blood out of every orifice,
你认为只是血管问题?
you think it just might be vascular?
血管炎?
Vasculitis?
如果我说是"章太"问题abc你会不会接着说"章太炎"?
If I had said it might be "vitas gerular,"abcwould you have said "vitas gerulaitis?"
检测血管炎 血管和血液
Test him for vasculitis,angio and blood.
即使找到了病因abc他还是要做肾脏移植
Even if we're right, he'sabcgonna need a kidney transplant.
测试她的女儿
Test the daughter.
她才12岁
She's 12.
肾脏小 意味着他可以少撒尿
Small kidney. It justabcmeans he won't pee as much.
外出旅游正合适
Great for road trips.
我是说她未成年 而爸爸有利益冲突abc我们需要Cuddy签字认可
I meant she's a minor and daddy has aabcconflict, so we're gonna need cuddy's sign off.
那去要呗
So get it.
她...似乎在忙
She's... kind of busy.
钳子
clamp.
吸管
Suction.
进入腹腔
Entering the abdominal cavity.
看到头了
There's the head.
有空么?
got a minute?
出去
Get out of here.
- 那是谁?abc- Gregory House医生
- Who's that?abc- Dr. Gregory house.
你得了脓血症后要去告的人
He's the one you'll beabcsuing when you develop sepsis.
他来干什么?
Well, why is he here?
你应该问她来干什么?
Better question is why is she here?
你是一名行政人员 负责管理
You're an administrator. Administrate.
- 病人的女儿需要法定监护人abc- 好了
- I have a patient's daughter needs a guardian ad litem.abc- That's it.
测试结果还未证实abc但无论如何他都要--
Tests are inconclusive.Butabceither way he's gonna need--
House 出去!
house, get out!
这儿不需要你 我需要
This doesn't need you. I do.
头出来了
Head's out.
- 等会儿abc- 再等就晚了
- Later.abc- Later's too late.
她出来了
And there she is.
求求你 哭啊
come on, cry.
求求你
Come on.
求求你 Joy 哭吧
Come on. Joy, cry.
哭吧 Joy
Cry, joy.
对不起
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
这是我们想听到的声音
that's the sound we like to hear
Apgar评分9分
apgar's nine out of ten.
听到了吗?
You hear that?
你得到了第一个"A"
You just got your first "A."
她是...你的了
She's... yours now.
恭喜你(希伯来语)
Mazel tov.
接下来你该对她说那句abc她得听上一辈子的话了
Now it's time to say those magic words you'llabcbe telling her for the rest of her life.
"妈妈要忙去了"
Mommy's gotta go to work.
他们向你解释过abc移植手术会带来什么风险吗?
have the risks of the transplantabcprocedure been explained to you?
见鬼 还指望你别告诉她呢
Damn it. I was hopingabcyou weren't going to ask her that.
她当然知道abc你把文件签了不就完事了?
Of course she knows. Canabcyou just sign the paperwork?
House医生告诉过你一切手术abc都有风险么? 你可能会死的
Dr. House explained to you that allabcsurgeries carry risk? You could die.
如果你不这么做 你老爸就死定了
And if you don't do it,daddy will die.
别强迫她
Stop pressuring her.
抱歉 你老爸好得很
Sorry. Daddy's perfectly healthy.
但无论如何我们都想让你abc再给他一个肾 有三个肾多酷啊
But we want you to give him a kidneyabcanyway because it'd be cool if he had three.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你知道只靠一个肾生活有多危险么?
Do you understand the risks ofabcliving with one kidney?
我知道
Yeah.
你仍旧愿意进行移植?
And you still want toabcproceed with the transplant?
是的
Yeah.
好吧 做吧
Okay, go ahead.
不行
No.
我是说 你可以继续了
I'm saying you can proceed.
我是说 我不能继续
I'm saying I can't.
不管他得了什么病 她也得了
Whatever he has,she has too.
她在梦游
She's sleepwalking.
如果不给他肾移植 他一周内就会死
if we don't give him a newabckidney, he's dead in a week.
必须给他移植
We have to transplant.
遥控器没电了换个没电的电池还是没用
When your remote has a dead battery, youabcdon't replace it with another dead battery.
不论是什么破坏了父亲的肾abc它也会破坏这孩子的肾脏
Whatever's killing the dad'sabckidneys is gonna kill the kid's too.
也许梦游症在病理上并不相关
It is possible the sleepabcissues aren't medically related.
也许他们由于公路噪音都患有失眠症
Maybe they're both insomniacsabcdue to the turnpike noise.
也许他们都是咖啡喝多了 也许...
Maybe they both drink tooabcmuch coffee, maybe--
House是对的
house is right.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
孩子也出现了汗血
Because the daughter's sweating blood.
症状相同 就意味着病因一致
If they have the same thing, itabcmeans there has to bea common cause.
也就是说 可能是毒素 感染 或者遗传
Which means it has to be aabctoxin, infection, or genetic.
而我们已排除了感染和毒素的可能...
And since we've ruledabcoutinfections and toxins--
那也只是"缩小"到了无数abc遗传性障碍中的某一种
it narrows it down to anyabcone of a dozen genetic disorders,
每个检测都要花一个多星期
each of which takesabcmore than a week to run.
给Foreman打个电话 动手干吧
Call foreman. Get to work.
Cuddy高兴得满面红光
cuddy is positively aglow.
你怎么解释?
What's your theory?
她只是装开心来惹你生气?
She's only acting happyabcto make you miserable?
我得找个遗传病
I need a genetic disease.
我敢肯定你早就有了
I'm sure you're carrying a few.
症状有肾衰竭 出血 失眠
Symptoms are kidneyabcfailure,bleeding, and insomnia.
你赌资都付清了?
You paid off the pool?
严格说来 谁没打赌 谁就是赢家
Technically, anyone whoabcdidn't enter is a winner.
还没完呢
It's not over yet.
本来大家都挺开心 直到打开那礼物
Everyone's happy untilabcthey unwrap that pretty present
是个非洲大陆形状的挂钟
and find they got a wallabcclock in the shape of africa.
领养就是欺骗 记得吗?
Adoption's a cheat,remember?
没有真正怀孕 就没有多巴胺受体的紊乱
There's no real pregnancy, so there'sabcno stranded dopamine receptors,
也不会有产后抑郁
so there's no postpartum depression.
Cuddy将会是你见过最快乐的新妈妈
Cuddy will be the happiest newabcmother you've ever seen.
我刚才解答了你的困惑 是吧?
I've just given you theabcanswer, haven't I?
现在你就要一言不发地冲出去了
And now you're going to walk outabcof here without saying a word.
才不是呢!
Nope!
好消息
good news.
我知道你们得了什么病abc你们俩都会痊愈的
I know what you have, andabcyou're both gonna be fine.
什么? 你是说真的?
What? Are you serious?
是又不是
Yes and no.
- 你知道他们得了什么病?abc- 没错
- So you do know what they have?abc- Yeah.
但是他们不能好起来?
but they aren't gonna be fine?
不知道 也许吧
No idea. They might be.
那你刚干嘛说可以痊愈?
Why the hell would you say they were?
让他们开心呗
To make them happy.
就开心两秒钟?
for two seconds?
确切地说 是看他们能不能开心
Technically, to seeabcif they can be happy.
本该看到一个微笑 眼波的闪动abc释然的叹息 之类的
We should've seen a grin, a twinkle,abca sigh of relief, something.
他们生病了 也很累了
They're sick. They're tired.
他们是快感缺失 无法感受快乐
They're anhedonic, incapableabcof experiencing pleasure.
他们体内的多巴胺受体受损
Something's bushwhackedabctheir dopamine receptors.
他们是沮丧
They're depressed.
母亲去世了 父亲奄奄一息
Mom's dead. Dad's dying.
要知道 沮丧不一定就是病状
You should know that being bummedabcisn't necessarily a pathology.
沮丧无法解释他们为什么abc没有朋友 对彼此冷漠
Being bummed doesn't explain their lack ofabcfriends or their indifference to each other.
为什么他们家没有音乐 风景 装饰
Why their place had noabcmusic, no view, no decor.
但如果你无法感受到快乐abc吸食可卡因又是为了什么?
But if you can't feel pleasure,abcwhat's with the cocaine?
真的? 你就是因此嗑药的?
Really? Is that why you do drugs?
因为你很快乐?
Because you're happy?
大部分人嗑药 是因为想变得快乐
Most people do 'em becauseabcthey want to be happy.
他潜意识里渴望得到快乐
His subconscious craved it,needed it.
快感缺失的病因通常是精神分裂
Most common cause ofabcanhedonia is schizophrenia.
没错 但仅限于白人
Sure, in white folk.
他们是黑人?
They're black?
他们撒了谎
They're liars.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
Jerry Harmon
Jerry harmon.
是问你的真名abc是Hosarian么? Herzog?
Your real name. Hosarian? Herzog?
哈里巴巴?
H'ali-baba?
是Hammoud
Hammoud.
Jamal Hammoud
Jamal hammoud.
国家第一次侵略伊拉克时改的
Changed it when we invadedabciraq the first time.
你怎么知道?
How'd you know?
你和你的女儿都得了家族性地中海热
You and your daughter haveabcfamilial mediterranean fever.
是地中海地区的家族遗传病
It's a genetic disease contractedabcby people of mediterranean descent.
犹太人 亚美尼亚人 阿拉伯人
Sephardic jews,armenians, arabs.
导致快感缺失 癫痫 肾衰竭abc甚至乳糖不耐症
Causes anhedonia,seizures, kidneyabcfailure, even lactose intolerance.
年龄增长或压力都会触发病状
Symptoms are set off by age and stress.
孩子无法快乐abc她会因为父亲快死了而感觉到压力
Kid couldn't get happy, but sheabccould get stressed by daddy dying.
你不知道我们能不能好起来?
You don't know if we'll get better?
一旦发展到汗血阶段 治疗就只能碰运气了
Treatment tends to be hit and missabconce you reach the sweating blood stage.
给他们用秋水仙碱和美法仑
Start them on colchicine and melphalan.
他的肾脏一塌糊涂
His kidneys are fried.
如果不是家族性地中海热abc秋水仙碱会导致他死亡
If he doesn't have fmf,theabccolchicine will kill him.
天 真希望我是对的
Boy, sure hope I'm right.
Harmon先生?
Mr. Harmon?
Harmon先生 请睁开眼睛
Mr. Harmon, I need you to open your eyes.
感觉好点么?
Feeling better?
Samantha怎么样了?
How's samantha?
她很好 可以给你进行肾移植了
Healthy enough to toss you a kidney.
爸爸?
Dad?
Sammy
Sammy.
宝宝一切良好
The baby's doing great.
我...
I...
我无法想像这对你有多难
I can't imagine howabchard this must be for you.
我... 我很傻很自私
I was--I wasabcstupid and selfish.
你是害怕
You were scared.
是啊 但你就不会
Yeah, but you wouldn't have been.
那可不一定
That's not true.
我是说 你当然会害怕 但是...
Well, I mean,you would'veabcbeen scared, but...
你总能做出正确的选择
you would've done the right thing anyway.
我也想这样
And I want to be like that.
我不想... 不想做个窝囊废
I don't--I don'tabcwant to be a loser.
你不是窝囊废
You're not a loser.
当我看见你抱着她 你脸上的表情
When I saw you hold herabcand the look on your face,
是我所见过最美的画面
it was the most beautifulabcthing I've ever seen.
那时我才意识到...
And that's when I realized...
我做不到
I can't.
Becca
Becca.
我的生活一直充满痛苦 愤怒和失望
My life, it's always been aboutabcpain, and anger, and disappointment,
从来没有爱
never about love.
那时我才意识到 我可以拥有爱
And that's when I realized,abcyou know, it could be.
我不能就此放弃
And I can't give that away.
Becca 不要这么做
Becca, don't do this.
你所感受到的 都合情合理
what you're feeling is natural.
但你现在被荷尔蒙 情绪abc还有忧虑所控制 而且...
But you're filled with hormones,andabcemotion, and fear, and...
你现在不能做这样重大的决定abc你要花些时间去考虑
you just can't make a huge decision likeabcthis right now. You have to give it some time.
我...
I am...
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
这决定将会颠覆一切
It's a decision that changes everything.
将改变你的余生
Changes the rest of your life.
希望如此
I hope so.
* 请不要夺走 我的阳光 *
* Don't take away my shine *
* 这缕阳光 是我拥有的一切 *
* my shine is all I have *
* 激情 爱情 美好 快乐 *
* my heat, my love,abcmy beauty,and my glad *
* 我渴望爱情 但常因此忧虑 *
* It worries me sometimesabcthat I want love *
* 我的生活 因此陷入哀伤 *
* and live a life of sad *
* 我用微颤的声线 *
* my tremolo *
* 歌唱你给我的热情 *
* sweet baby my fire *
现在不适合你来幸灾乐祸
It's really not theabcgreatest time for gloating.
"天涯何处无宝宝"嘛
There's more than one baby in the sea.
乱搞的小子多得是呢
The world is full ofabcteenage boys riding bareback.
不 我不想再试了
No. I'm done.
我无法承受再重来一次
I can't go through that again.
你要放弃
You're quitting.
跟你放弃体外受精一样
Just like you quit ivf.
是啊 就跟那一样
Yeah, just like that.
呐 你又重来了一次
There, you just did it again.
真是太糟了
It's too bad.
你本可以做个好妈妈的
You would've made a great mother.
你这混账!
You son of a bitch.
我试着要孩子的时候abc你说我当妈妈肯定糟透了
When I was getting a baby, youabctold meI'd suck as a mother.
现在我要不到了 你却说我能做个好妈妈
Now that I've lost it, youabctell me I'd be great as a mother.
你干嘛总是跟我对着干?
Why do you need to negate everything?
我也不知道
I don't know.
晚安
Good night.